ROBIN TEN BERGE

Vuursteenhof 13 1349 EJ Almere

M: +31 6 43 90 68 38 E: robin@rtbprojects.com

https://www.linkedin.com/ in/robintenberge

https://github.com/rbergenl

Technical Skills

NodeJS

HTML5 / CSS3 / ES6

React / Angular

Azure / AWS

CI/CD

Soft Skills

Communicative

Proactive

Problem solving

Team player

Structured

Certificates

Mobile Web Specialist 2019

AWS DevOps Pro 2019

Java SE8 2017

Scrum Developer 2016

Profile

Robin is a senior full stack web developer with 10+ years experience developing cloud-, pipeline-, frontend- and backend solutions. He is focussed on being productive to deliver high quality products while using best practices. He enjoys helping team members and has a desire to share his gained insights.

Robin has excellent communication skills and knows how to find his way within an organisation. He is a pioneer and takes initiatives to help move an organisation forward with innovation. He embraces new technology, puts them into practice and keeps educating himself.

Scrum Master - "You know how to challenge the team. You have a clear opinion on quality and productivity. And in this way you help bring the team to a higher level."

Product Owner - "Robin is able to take responsibility for a solution. He likes to take the lead in creating a collaborative solution and then also delivers it."

Experience

Senior Web Developer, RTB Projects; Almere — 2009 - Present Freelancing with the goal to deliver web development and IT consultancy to small and large companies.

- Received expert score of the React assessment on Pluralsight by being in the top 2%. Published a React Native application to Google Play Store. And created own website rtbprojects.com with a React framework.
- Created a full e-commerce solution with PHP to sell products via internet. This includes frontend and a backend for inventory, order and payment processing (WooCommerce did not exist yet).
- Provided IT consultancy to small companies. This includes support with webhosting and delivery of new Wordpress websites, SEO and analytics implementation.

Senior Full Stack Developer, NS, Utrecht — 2019 - Present Worked as full stack developer in a team responsible for travel information on the website.

- Proactively took a leading role in the migration to AWS Cloud.
 Refactored API's to Kotlin and Docker. Deployed Angular frontends from a NX monorepo, while improving CI/CD pipelines.
- Collaborated with architects and helped other teams to get started with their migration.
- The team received a DevOps status, being an example to the organisation.

Senior Consultant, Capgemini, Amsterdam — 2014 - 2019

Worked as web developer at ABN AMRO in Amsterdam. All assignments were in a complex Agile/
Scrum environment with Offshore.

For the Commercial Banking department:

- Lead in setting up the frontend architecture utilising the NodeJS ecosystem. Collaborated with other teams to share the architecture.
- Initiated an organisational change to upgrade the Java web application by pitching a Proof of Concept to management. This upgrade was needed to be able to work with DevOps teams.
- Had a business trip to Hyderabad in India to provide knowledge transfer to the Offshore team.

For the Retail department:

- Delivered the first Angular widget for mobile friendly Internet Banking. Collaborated with architects on setting up the frontend for Angular widgets.
- Setup the framework for unit- and e2e-testing with a RESTful stub-server with ExpressJs.

 Shared it with other teams so they can perform better testing and comply with quality guidelines.
- Setup the foundation for a technical style guide with reusable UI components. Supported other teams in using the frontend architecture and reusable components so they can build and deliver faster.

Project Leader, Wageningen University & Research; Wageningen — 2012 - 2013

Responsible for two IT projects. One Prince2 project to deliver an IT Selfservice Portal. And a
Scrum project to deliver a workflow application for an internal customer. The activities included
making project plans, supporting the teams and communicating with stakeholders.

Education

Windesheim University of Applied Sciences, Zwolle – Business Information Technology, Bachelor degree - 2005 - 2008

- Graduated with honour and one year shortened.
- Had two internships. One in New Zealand at Jack & Di's Lakeview Accommodation to optimise
 the reservation process and systems (grade: A+). And a final internship at Ernst & Young to
 develop a method to conduct strategic business information planning (grade: A+).

Additional

Interested in other cultures and meeting new people by doing volunteering projects or adventurous travel. For example backpacking in New Zealand (2007) and a hitchhike trip to Asia (2008).

Played basketbal for a while (2000-2014), moved to triathlon (2014-2020) and this year started with basketbal again.

Became a husband (2020) and a father (2021).

Skill Matrix	Knowledge (level)			Experience (years)
Frontend				
HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript			Х	10+
NodeJs ecosystem			Х	7
ES6, Typescript and PWA's			Х	5
React and Angular (incl. Redux and NgRx)			Х	4
Testing frameworks: the latest being Jest and Cypress			Х	4
Backend				
ExpressJs (incl. OAuth, GraphQL and Swagger)		Х		5
Linux and Docker		Х		5
MySQL and MongoDB		Х		4
PHP and Java (Kotlin)		Х		3
Platforms				
Microsoft Azure			Х	2
Amazon Web Services			Х	4
Google Cloud Platform		Х		3
Practices				
Agile/Scrum			Х	9
CI/CD			Х	6
DevOps		Х		3